Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
2.1.4.3
Marist College
  Box 1570
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Advertising Club, circa 1930s; 1 (Box 1570)
    - [The Advertising Club], 1
  - Subject files: Afghanistan, 1921 - 1922; 2 (Box 1570)
    - [Five men in Afghanistan], 1
    - [Cars in Afghanistan], 2
    - [L.T. and party in the city of Kabul, Afghanistan], 3
  - Subject files: Airplane crash, 1920s; 3 (Box 1570)
    - Note [Letter to Jack from Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [Airplane crash], 2
    - [Airplane crash], 3
    - [Airplane crash], 4
  - Subject files: Airplanes, 1920s; 4 (Box 1570)
    - [Airplane on a runway], 1
    - [Airplane on the ground], 2
    - [Airplane in water], 3
    - [Airplane taking off in water], 4
    - [Group of people gathered by an airplane], 5
    - [Two pilots in a plane], 6
    - [Airplane parked at a dock], 7
    - [People standing on a plane], 8
    - [People standing on a plane], 9
    - [Aviator standing next to a plane], 10
    - [An airplane taking off], 11
    - [People gathered around an airplane], 12
    - [People standing by a plane], 13
    - [People standing on a plane], 14
    - [Airplane], 15
    - [Town waterway], 16
    - [Sailboat in icy water], 17
    - [Buildings beside the waterway], 18
    - [Building in the middle of the street], 19
    - [Building on the water], 20
    - [Trolley], 21
    - [Canal and windmill], 22
    - [Building on the water], 23
    - [Town on the banks of the water], 24
  - Subject files: Airport Runway Photographs, circa 1950s; 5 (Box 1570)
    - [Group of men in front of an airplane on the runway], 1
    - [Group of men on the airplane runway], 2
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 6 (Box 1570)
    - [Four men on a mountain in Alaska], 1
    - [Man pushing a wheelbarrow in Alaska], 2
    - [Woman standing on a porch in Alaska], 3
    - [Boy sitting in a yard in Alaska], 4
    - [Woman and boy on a porch in Alaska], 5
    - [Man in front of a shop in Alaska], 6
    - [Neighborhood road in Alaska], 7
    - [Young boy standing in the street in Alaska], 8
    - [Man and boy standing by an automobile in Alaska], 9
    - [Woman standing in a yard in Alaska], 10
    - [Conductor of a train in the head car in Alaska], 11
    - [Man standing in the head car of a train in Alaska], 12
    - [Building, "A.B. No. 19" in Alaska], 13
    - [Building on the shore in Alaska], 14
    - [Man and a dog in Alaska], 15
    - [Three men standing outside in Alaska], 16
    - [Ferry boat in Alaska], 17
    - [Landscape of water and trees in Alaska], 18
    - [Man and woman sitting on a porch in Alaska], 19
    - [Two women standing outside of a building in Alaska], 20
    - [Young girl feeding pigeons in Alaska (?)], 21
    - [Three children at the beach (In Alaska?)], 22
    - [Woman and girl feeding pigeons in Alaska (?)], 23
    - [Woman with pigeons on her arms in Alaska (?)], 24
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 7 (Box 1570)
    - [Man on the bank, ferry in backgound, in Alaska], 1
    - [People on a dock in Alaska], 2
    - [People boaring a boat in Alaska], 3
    - [Men standing outside a building in Alaska, 4
    - [A family sitting on the sand in Alaska], 5
    - [Cliffs and water in Alaska], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) with pigeons on his arms in Alaska], 7
    - [Two young girls standing outside in Alaska], 8
    - [Two women on a boat in Alaska], 9
    - [View of the shore from a boat in Alaska], 10
    - [Ramp coming out of the water in Alaska], 11
    - [Woman and girl standing in front of a building in Alaska], 12
    - [Ferry boat in Alaska], 13
    - [Passage between two clifft in Alaska], 14
    - [Water and hills in Alaska], 15
    - [The shoreline in Alaska], 16
    - [Two women on a boat in Alaska], 17
    - [People on a porch in Alaska], 18
    - [People gathered on a porch in Alaska], 19
    - [Water and mountains in Alaska], 20
    - [A family on a porch in Alaska], 21
    - [Ferry in Alaska], 22
    - [Houses in Alaska], 23
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 8 (Box 1570)
    - [Man with a life jacket on in Alaska], 1
    - ["A Few Guns Soapy Smith Did Not Use."], 2
    - [People at the top of a hill in Alaska], 3
    - [People walking outside in Alaska], 4
    - [Sunset over the mountains in Alaska], 5
    - [Waterway in Alaska], 6
    - [Train in Alaska], 7
    - [People in a boat in Alaska], 8
    - [House in Alaska], 9
    - [People outside of a mine (?) in Alaska], 10
    - [House on stilts in the water in Alaska], 11
    - [House in Alaska], 12
    - [Houses in Alaska], 13
    - [Ship in Alaska], 14
    - [Man scaling a cliff in Alaska], 15
    - [Snowy mountains in Alaska], 16
    - [Town in Alaska], 17
    - [Landscape in Alaska], 18
    - [Water and mountains in Alaska], 19
    - [Boat in Alaska], 20
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 9 (Box 1570)
    - [Man and woman standing on a boat in Alaska], 1
    - [Three men walking on a dock in Alaska], 2
    - [White rapids in Alaska], 3
    - [View of mountains from a boat in Alaska], 4
    - Farm in Alaska with snowy mountains in the distance], 5
    - [View of snowy mountains in Alaska from a boat], 6
    - [Two women on the porch of a log cabin in Alaska], 7
    - [People in boats in Alaska], 8
    - [Large boat in Alaska], 9
    - [Automobile driving down a dirt road in Alaska], 10
    - [Livestock in Alaska], 11
    - [White rapids in Alaska], 12
    - [Remains of a forest in Alaska], 13
    - [A building in progress in Alaska], 14
    - [Automobile on the side of the road in Alaska], 15
    - [Wooden suspension bridge in Alaska], 16
    - [Man climbing up a rock face in Alaska], 17
    - [People on a boat in Alaska], 18
    - [Ferry boat in Alaska], 19
    - [Boats moored in the water in Alaska], 20
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 10 (Box 1570)
    - Note [Checked by L.T. Sat June 13 '81], 1
    - Note [Envelope from Lowell Thomas to The National Bank of Pawling. 1914 is- Alaska negatives], 2
    - Note [There is a lot of stuff down in the "Board" room at H H for framing. We should look 'em over., 3
    - [People gathered on a dock in Alaska], 4
    - [Automobile outside of the Miner's Home Hotel and Roadhouse in Alaska], 5
    - [Three men trying to get an automobile out of the grass (?)], 6
    - [Four men on a rocky shore in Alaska], 7
    - [Automobile driving down a dirt road in Alaska], 8
    - [Boat in Alaska], 9
    - [Man posing in front of a boat on land in Alaska], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas on a bridge in Alaska], 11
    - [The Miners Home Hotel and Roadhouse in Alaska], 12
    - [Man standing in front of a boat in Alaska], 13
    - [Man checking the engine of an automobile in Alaska], 14
    - [Woman standing on some rocks in Alaska], 15
    - [A river in Alaska], 16
    - [An automobile on a dirt road in Alaska], 17
    - [A building with a crane (?) in Alaska], 18
    - [Native Alaskans gathered around a camera], 19
    - [Trying to get their automobile out of the mud in Alaska], 20
    - [A man driving a car through the streets of an Alaskan town], 21
    - [Woman leaning on a boat in Alaska], 22
    - [Two native Alaskans in kayaks], 23
    - [McClusky's Roadhouse in Alaska], 24
    - [A river running through cliffs in Alaska], 25
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1915 - 1916; 11 (Box 1570)
    - Note [Envelope "Extras"], 1
    - [Girl standing in front of "Tolovana" in Alaska], 2
    - [Children with a dog pulling a wagon in Alaska], 3
    - [Church with "Free Public Reading Room" in Alaska], 4
    - [Church in Alaska], 5
    - [Three men standing by canoes in Alaska], 6
    - A group of people in Alaska], 7
    - [Group of men and a woman in Alaska], 8
    - [Aerial view of a town in Alaska], 9
    - [Two women standing on a pier in Alaska], 10
    - [Men in Alaska], 11
    - [Docks in Alaska], 12
    - [People in Alaska playing a game], 13
    - [Man in Alaska standing by his garden], 14
    - [Lake and mountains in Alaska, 15
    - [Two women on a boat in Alaska], 16
  - Subject files: Alaska (petrified forest), circa 1915 - 1916; 12 (Box 1570)
    - [Man inspecting a tree trunk in the petrified forest in Alaska], 1
    - [Man sitting on a tree trunk in the petrified forest in Alaska], 2
    - [Man srtanding in the petrified forest in Alaska], 3
    - Note [13 negatives of the Petrified Forest. Lowell J. Thomas], 4
  - Subject files: Alaska (Lowell Thomas), circa 1915 - 1916; 13 (Box 1570)
    - [Lowell Thomas pointing at something in Alaska], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas filming in Alaska], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a man and woman on a boat in Alaska], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a fur coat in Alaska], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a fur coat in Alaska], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas standing on a boat in Alaska], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas on top of a mountain in Alaska], 7
  Box 1571
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Alaska (Vance photographs), 1929 - 1930; 1 (Box 1571)
    - [Man and his dog in Alaska], 1
    - [Man next to a totem pole in Alaska], 2
    - [Man and his dog in Alaska], 3
    - [Man with hat standing outside of an automobile in Alaska], 4
    - [Man standing outside of an automobile in Alaska], 5
    - [Man standing next to a tree in Alaska], 6
    - [Man and two boys sitting in Alaska], 7
    - [Man and his two boys sitting on a bench in Alaska], 8
    - [Man sitting on bench next to a totem pole in Alaska], 9
    - [Man and woman sitting on benches in Alaska], 10
    - [Man and a woman sitting on a bench in Alaska], 11
    - [Man petting his dog in Alaska], 12
  - Subject files: Alaska [glass negatives], 1950; 2 (Box 1571)
    - [Four men standing in front of a "Rescue" plane in Alaska], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man in Alaska], 2
    - [City in Alaska], 3
    - [Man and woman standing outside of a shop in Alaska], 4
    - [Man standing outside of a shop in Alaska], 5
  - Subject files: Alaska [glass negatives], 1950; 3 (Box 1571)
    - [Two men talking on a city street in Alaska], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of a plane in Alaska], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and three men standing outside of a "Rescue" plane in Alaska], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man standing in front of the Resuce plane in Alaska], 4
  - Subject files: Alaska, circa 1950s; 4 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in a broken engine in Alaska], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas Jr. sitting in a broken engine in Alaska], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 12
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas on skis and two men next to planes in Alaska], 14
  - Subject files: Alaska - Lowell Thomas, Jr., circa 1964; 5 (Box 1571)
    - [Three people standing outside of a plane in Alaska], 1
  - Subject files: Amos 'N Andy, 1959; 6 (Box 1571)
    - Note [Wide World Photo Amons 'N' Andy--20 Years Ago-12/28/48], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting at a table with Amos and Andy], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting with Amos and Andy at a table], 3
    - [Amos and Andy doing a radio broadcast], 4
  - Subject files: Ancestors, circa late 1800s - 1900; 7 (Box 1571)
    - Harry G. Thomas, 1
    - [Portrait of a man and woman-ancestors], 2
    - [A family portrait-ancestors], 3
    - [Portrait of a man and woman-anscestors], 4
    - [Portrait of Samuel Slats (?)-ancestors], 5
  - Subject files: Antarctica, 1956 - 1966; 8 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with three men in Antartica], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas shaking hands with a man from a plane in Antartica], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and a pilot standing in on a runway in Antartica], 3
  - Subject files: General Henry "Hap" Arnold and Lowell Thomas, 1927; 9 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas and General Henry "Hap" Arnold standing next to a plane], 1
  - Subject files: Bohemian Grove, circa 1961 - 1962; 10 (Box 1571)
    - August 21, 1962, Here's another picture from the Bohemian Grove, 1
    - Note: August 21, 1962, Here's another picture from the Bohemian Grove, 2
    - The Redwood History of Man, 3
    - Note: The Redwood History of Man, 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and friends at the Bohemian Grove], 5
  - Subject files: Leon Blum, Premier of France, and Lowell Thomas, circa 1936 - 1938; 11 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Leon Blum looking over papers], 1
  - Subject files: Broadcasting, circa 1930s; 12 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a radio broadcast], 1
  - Subject files: Broadcasting, 1941 September 9; 13 (Box 1571)
    - Lowell Thomas at microphone (NBC) #5, 1
    - Lowell Thomas at microphone (NBC) #6, 2
    - Lowell Thomas at microphone (NBC) #9, 3
    - Lowell Thomas at microphone (NBC) #11, 4
    - Note [Thomas, Lowell-#5. At microphone], 5
  - Subject files: Broadcasting, 1930s - circa 1950s; 14 (Box 1571)
    - Broadcasting 1930s, 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and man doing a NBC broadcast], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and man broadcasting over NBC], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 6
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 8
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 9
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man doing a NBC broadcast], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas whispering in a man's ear during a NBC broadcast], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a NBC broadcast with a dog], 12
    - Note [Lowell Thomas at Cloverbrook studio], 13
    - [Lowell Thomas with a group of people], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas and a group of men doing a CBS broadcast], 15
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas doing a CBS broadcast], 16
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a NBC broadcast], 17
    - [Lowell Thomas interviewing a man during a CBS broadcast], 18
  - Subject files: Prosper Buranelli [passport photograph], undated; 15 (Box 1571)
    - [Prosper Buranelli's passport photo], 1
    - Note [Prosper-1-4X5 Passport Neg.], 2
  - Subject files: Robert Campbell, circa 1940s; 16 (Box 1571)
    - [Portrait of Robert Campbell], 1
    - Note [Campbell, Robert J. Lt. Col. FV885912. Translation Get 6 contacts with 1/2" border at bottom], 2
  - Subject files: Capital Cities, undated; 17 (Box 1571)
    - N.Y. Stock Exchange, 1
    - N.Y. Stock Exchange, 2
  - Subject files: Cartoons, undated; 18 (Box 1571)
    - [Drawing of Lowell Thomas], 1
    - [The New Yorker "The Talk of the Town"], 2
    - Caricature of Lowell Thomas], 3
    - ["Week Will Bring Better Fare" with a sketch of Lowell Thomas], 4
    - [Small cartoon of Lowell Thomas], 5
    - ["I know you! You're the star of Lowell Thomas's show!" cartoon], 6
    - [Cartoon of Lowell Thomas], 7
    - [Caricature of Lowell Thomas], 8
    - [Drawing of Lowell Thomas], 9
    - [Caricature of Lowell Thomas], 10
    - Note [A London cartoon when he was putting on his "Allenby-Lawrence production at Covent Garden Opera House in 1918. He has been cartooned scores of times-here and abroad], 11
    - ["Gran'Pappy's got Lowell Thomas in thar with him-they're talkin' over plane fer next summer's soft ball season." cartoon], 12
    - ["To Lowell Thomas. (?), Explorer, World Traveller & Bath Bush Impressario from Fred Anderson". cartoon], 13
    - [Cartoon of Lowell Thomas being chased by a snake], 14
    - [Cartoon referencing Lowell Thomas's softball team], 15
    - [Cartoon of Lowell Thomas broadcasting], 16
    - [Cartoon of Lowell Thomas and another man hitting their heads while skiing.], 17
    - [The New Yorker "The Talk of thr Town" Lowell Thomas cartoon], 18
    - ['Lowell Thomas on the tallest elephant you ever saw, shows you the sights of Nepal and Kashmir in Cinerama's "Search for Paradise" at the Music Hall" Cartoon], 19
    - [Cartoon of a skiier rolling down a mountain in a giant snowball], 20
  - Subject files: China, undated; 19 (Box 1571)
    - [Group of people in China], 1
  - Subject files: Cinerama, 1950s; 20 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man and woman looking at a Cinerama program], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and a man sitting at a banquet table], 2
  - Subject files: Cinerama (Indus River - Christopher Young, photographer), circa 1956; 21 (Box 1571)
    - Note: Cinerama-Indus River (Christopher Young, photographer. Negatives of Indus River, 1
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 2
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 3
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 4
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 5
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 6
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 7
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 8
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 9
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 10
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 11
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 12
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 13
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 14
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 15
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 16
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 17
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 18
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 19
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 20
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 21
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 22
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 23
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 24
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 25
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 26
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 27
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 28
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 29
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 30
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 31
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 32
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 33
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 34
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 35
    - [Rafting the Indus River for Cinerama, Search for Paradise], 36
  - Subject files: Cinerama (Lowell Thomas and President Dwight D. Eisenhower), 1955; 22 (Box 1571)
    - [Lowell Thomas and President Dwight D. Eisenhower at Cinerama], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and President Dwight D. Eisenhower at Cinerama], 2
  Box 1572
- Subject Files, 2.1.4.3
  - Subject files: Clover Brook, circa 1920s; 1 (Box 1572)
    - [View of Clover Brook], 1
    - [View of Clover Brook], 2
    - [View of Clover Brook], 3
    - [Clover Brook house], 4
    - [Clover Brook land], 5
    - [Tree at Clover Brook], 6
    - [House at Clover Brook], 7
    - [The Clover Brook house], 8
    - [The house at Clover Brook], 9
    - [The house at Clover Brook], 10
    - [The Clover Brook house], 11
    - [House at Clover Brook], 12
    - [The house at Clover Brook], 13
    - [the house at Clover Brook], 14
    - [The Clover Brook estate], 15
  - Subject files: Clover Brook (Provensen event), circa 1927; 2 (Box 1572)
    - [Pool at the Clover Brook estate], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas's soft ball team], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas's soft ball team], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a pumpkin], 4
    - [Man standing next to a horse], 5
    - [Lowell Thomas wearing a hat], 6
    - [Man and woman on horseback], 7
    - [Man riding a horse], 8
    - [Woman standing next to a pumpkin], 9
    - [Woman and a dog standing next to a pumpkin], 10
    - [Lowell Thomas standing next to a pumpkin], 11
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with a pumpkin], 12
    - [Man on horseback], 13
    - [The boys playing instruments], 14
    - [Lowell Thomas sitting in the library with his dog], 15
    - [Mounted portrait of a Prince William of Sweden] Caption: To Mr. and Mrs. Lowell Thomas, with best thanks for a few very pleasant days at Clover Brook,. January 1927 [signed] Prince William of Sweden, 16
  - Subject files: College Days, circa 1909 - 1912; 3 (Box 1572)
    - [Portrait of a man in a top hat], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other boys], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and three other boys], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas (?) in his dorm room], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas standing with four women], 5
    - Note [The Triennial Reunion of the Alpha Epsilon Franternity invitation], 6
  - Subject files: College Degrees, undated; 4 (Box 1572)
    - [Lowell Thomas and Herbert Hoover in graduation gowns], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and Herbert Hoover asleep at a commencement ceremony], 2
    - [Photos of Lowell Thomas at Ohio Wesleyan graduation where he received an honorary doctorate], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas receiving honorary doctorate at Ohio Wesleyan], 4
  - Subject files: Cripple Creek, Victor Colorado, undated; 5 (Box 1572)
    - [Victor,Colorado], 1
    - [Victor, Colorado, City of Gold Mines], 2
    - [Landscape of Victor, Colorado], 3
    - [Town of Victor, Colorado], 4
    - [Crowd of people going to the mines in Victor, Colorado], 5
    - [Group of men standing outside of a cabin in Cripple Creek, Victor Colorado], 6
    - [House in Cripple Creek, Victor Colorado], 7
    - [Lowell Thomas standing in front of railroad tracks in Cripple Creek, Victor Colorado], 8
    - Note [LT when editor of the daily paper, in Colorado in 1911-12.], 9
    - [Wrestling team (?)], 10
  - Subject files: Mary Davis, circa late 1950s - 1960; 6 (Box 1572)
    - [Aiken gravestone], 1
    - [Mary Davis and two other women], 2
    - [Mary Davis sitting in a living room], 3
  - Subject files: Dionne quintuplets, Canada, 1941; 7 (Box 1572)
    - [Lowell Thomas doing a broadcast with children], 1
    - Note [LT, Narse (?) Cheput (?), F. Daris Benken, Mary Davis in Quints' nursery in Collendar, Ontatio on their 7th birthday, May 1941 (?)], 2
    - Note [Press Release: Cecile Inching Ahead in Quintuplet Growth Race], 3
    - Note [Press Release: The Quintuplets Get a New Nurse], 4
  - Subject files: Dog monument, circa 1960s; 8 (Box 1572)
    - [Lowell Thomas and his son at the Dog monument], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and his son petting the Dog monument, 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and his son at the Dog monument], 3
    - [Lowell Thomas and his son at the Dog monument], 4
    - [Lowell Thomas and his son at the Dog monument], 5
  - Subject files: Dogs, undated; 9 (Box 1572)
    - [Lowell Thomas giving his god a treat], 1
    - [Lowell Thomas and his dog], 2
    - [Lowell Thomas and his dog], 3
  - Subject files: Dick Durrance, undated; 10 (Box 1572)
    - [Dick Durrance skiing], 1
  - Subject files: Early Atlantic fliers (Charles Lindbergh, Clarence D. Chamberlin, Amelia Earhart and others), circa 1930s; 11 (Box 1572)
    - [The Early Atlantic fliers], 1